berlinlasers.com 2014-04-25

# Privacy Policy | Berlinlasers

**Privacy Policy**

 **To our Individual Clients:**  
Berlin Lasers is committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring you a positive experience on our website. Your privacy is important to us, and maintaining your trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities. We respect your right to keep your personal information confidential and understand your desire to avoid unwanted solicitations. We hope that by taking a few minutes to read it, you will have a better understanding of what we do with the information you provide us and how we keep it private and secure. 

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.   
When you are taking an order on our site, as appropriate, we may collect the following information:  
 **During Registration:**   
● Your first name, last name and middle initial  
● Company name if possible  
● Email address  
● Zip code  
 **During the purchase process:**  
● Credit card number and expiration date  
● billing address  
● shipping address

 **What we do with information collected?**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customers.   
Any of the information we collect for you may be used in one of the following ways:  
● Berlin Lasers may use your name, email, and postal address to send you information advising you of our upcoming events, new products, purchase status, features and Berlin Lasers sites and related information, but only if you give us your permission to do so.   
● To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.   
Note: It at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving further emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of email.   
● To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. 

**Security**  
Berlin Lasers is committed to ensuring the personal information your share with us secure. Our website has security measure in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. We utilize suitable security technology, procedures, and organizational measures to maintain the safety of your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

**Applicability of Policy**  
The privacy policy applies to Berlin Lasers site. In order to provide a more comprehensive and useful website, our site contains links to other website that are not under our control. Berlin Lasers is not responsible for the content of any linked website, any changes or updates to such website, or the privacy policies of such websites. Further, the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Berlin Lasers of that website and its terms and policies. 

**For More Information**  
Berlin Lasers will discontinue contact with any person upon oral or written request.   
If you have any further questions about our Privacy Policy, the information that we have collected from your online, the practice of this site, your interaction with this website or to correct and/or change contact information, please contact us at [support@berlinlasers.com](mailto:support@berlinlasers.com).
